I'm still up to lead dance, rising up through the air
I pay head in the distance, so is she more in light
I hit the heavy on my side, you're dead
I had to stop for the night, then she stood in the doorway
Her division bell, then I was thinking to myself
This could be heaven, this could be hell
Didn't you lift up back and up?
And she showed me the way
Then we'll voices down the corridor
Thought I heard them say
Welcome to the hotel California
Thought you'd love me, please
Maybe time will come
You can find it here
Her mind is different and twisted
She got the Mercedes-Benz ball
She got a lot of pretty pretty boys
She calls friends
How they dance in the courtyard
Sweet summer sweat
So dance to remember
Some dance to forget
So I'm calling the captain
Please bring me my wine
We have it in that desperate list
In 1960, man
And still those voices are calling for fire
Hey
Make you laugh in the middle of the night
Just till you then say
Welcome to the hotel California
Thought you'd love me, please
Mirrors on this ceiling
You can't champion on ice
And she said
We were all just prisoners here
Of our own device
And in the master's chambers
Gathered for their feast
The stabbit with their stealing eyes
But they just can't kill the beast
Last thing I remember
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
Relaxed at the nightmare
We are a problem to receive
You can check out at it's time you like
But you can never leave
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before
I was running for the gold
I had to find a passage back
To the place I was before